{
    "id": "db02861adbf94b65b69352d148524353",
    "title": "Because And Because Of",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We cancelled the trip ..................... the rain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He sat down ………………….. he was feeling dizzy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It is …………………. your mother that we got into this mess.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We hurried indoors ……………….. it was raining.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I was late …………………. the traffic.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We could not reach on time ………………… the traffic was terrible.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The exam was easy ...................... he knew all the answers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He can’t walk .....................… his illness.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He lost his job ...................... the recession.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. the language problem, I couldn’t win the argument.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Because of",
                "Because"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}